So something I hear quite often is people saying, you know, we need to have unity, we need to come
together, we need to have community, but so often folks either don't know or aren't ready to take
the steps that need to happen in order to make that happen. I'm Amanda Seals and I want to tell
you about the MLK League and the work that they're doing to do exactly that. The League is a diverse
and intergenerational consortium of community leaders that are dedicated to working together
to create change on local levels. And the beauty of this is that we need this interconnectivity to
happen state to state across this nation and globally. That's why it's international. In
order for the violence associated with imperialism to be stopped in this track, it's going to take
us using our people power to come together to stop it. So join us June 14th through 16th for the
Silence the Violence Summit. We'll have events going on all week. And if you want to just be a part of
this organization and learn more, go to mlkleague.org. Let's get cracking. We got work to do.